Contact

- Kocaeli,41,41000
- 554 186 0611
- y.omerkara1136@gmail.c om
- www.linkedin.com/in/yasi n-ömer-kara/
- medium.com/@yomerkar
- github.com/yomerkara

Skills

Python

Kotlin Excellent Java Good MVVM 2021-07 -Very Good 2022-01 OOP Excellent C# Good



Yasin Ömer Kara

Cloud&Data Platforms Engineer

I'm just graduated from Kocaeli University Computer Engineering Department.

During my college years, I'm worked at Softtech as a Jr. Android Developer ,at Kocaeli University Image Processing Ar-Ge Lab as an Image Processing and Embedded System Researcher Intern and now at Koç Sistem as a Cloud&Data Platform Engineer.

You can reach the in-company projects I have done in the places I worked from my CV, and can reach my individual and university projects and certificates on GitHub(~directory name: AboutMe). And finally, you can find my articles about the new developments that I follow on Medium or the compilations about the topics that I am in the learning process.

Work History

2022-02 -2022-04

Intern Image Processing - Embedded Systems Ar-Ge Lab

Kocaeli University, Kocaeli Person, vehicle and traffic tracking software with drone.

- -Image Processing
- -Embedded System

Junior Android Developer

Softtech, Istanbul Projects I've worked on:

- -Triwi(Nanotechnological Breast Cancer Application)
- -2 ongoing mobile projects of İşbank

Very Good

Very Good

English

,000

2022-04 -Current Cloud&Data Platforms Engineer

Koç Sistem, Istanbul

• Education

2017-09 – 2022-06 Bachelor of Computer Engineering: Computer Engineering

Kocaeli University - Kocaeli